♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Holo-sphere system connected.
Welcome to Sector Five.
The wall’s gonna open any second now.
Let’s go!
Three minutes to find the key! Go!
Uh oh, the doors are in the wrong place.
Here come our old friends.
Creepers!
They just can’t stay away from us.
Remember guys, the clock is running.
Let’s see.
I found the key, at 2 o’clock directly above Yumi.
That’s a job for a cat.
(GRUNTING)
No so fast, dummy!
Odd, you’re running out of life points!
Odd!
(SCREAMING)
Nice one.
Now!
I’m connected, Jeremie.
Come on, Aelita,
we’ve gotta gather the data before the flying mantas come!
The mantas are about to hatch!
5, 4, 3, 2 ,1, Now!
Hey, Jeremie, I don’t see any flying mantas.
Strange, I can see them on my screen.
Stay on your guard,
they may come from the other end of the sector.
Done, Jeremie,
you can take over again.
Ok, I’m on it!
I’ve programmed the overbike.
Hang on, princess.
Ok, the passage is open.
Jeremie, we’ve got a problem.
We just found the flying mantas
You should be able to lose them.
But... what is that?
Mines, Jeremie, they’re hatching flying mines.
Phew
Well, these are codes for Xana’s sub-systems, I cracked them three weeks ago.
Hey, yeah! This one looks like the source code to a virus,
I might be able to use it!
If the virus inside you is anything like this one,
I might be able to free you from Xana.
You mean, like soon?
Yeah!
Ok, we’re outta here.
There’s a big climbing competition tonight, gotta practice.
I already told you, I’m not doing it.
Really?
Why not?
Cause.
At least come and watch me.
Come on, Ulrich,
for once Odd’s found a sport where being scrawny is a plus.
Hey, I am not scrawny, ha,
I’m svelte. It’s not the same.
Come on, keep it steady.
You shoulda left your zits down there, huh Herb?
They’re too heavy.
Della Robbia, I’m gonna…
(SCREAMS)
I’m the king of the world!
Ok Stern, the wall.
Uh, y-ysee Jim.
Huh?
First one to the top.
Sorry, I don’t climb.
Are you scared?
No I’m not scared, I--
Come on, Stern,. show us what you’ve got.
Get up that wall, hurry up!
Hey man, humiliate this guy and let’s go eat.
Ready Aelita?
Yes, the test worked.
It’s unbelievable.
We did it, we’ve got the anti-virus.
Jeremie, what if--
What if you injected me right now?
We could surprise the others.
But isn’t that a little risky?
It’ll be just as risky in two hours, or in two days.
Ok, go to the scanner, I’ll start the process.
What is he doing?
Hey, come on Ulrich, move it!
You can beat him, go for it, Ulrich!
Come on, huh, Spiderman?
You spinning a web? Or did you fall asleep?
Hey, Stern! What’s the matter with you?
(SCREAMING)
Oh, I get it, a little back before lunch, right?
Leave me alone.
Y-You’ve got vertigo, is that it?
Ulrich, wait!
Let him chill out a while,
give him time to get over it.
Ready?
Yes, do it.
Aelita, how do you feel?
Say something.
Something.
If you can make jokes as bad as Odd’s,
then you must be ok.
Ulrich?
Maybe he went to the factory to mope.
Hey, I’ve got great news!
We found the anti-virus,
and I’ve already given it to Aelita.
You’ve what?
That’s so great!
All we have to do now is shutdown the supercomputer,
and it’s adios to Xana.
Ok, but not without Ulrich,
we have to find him first.
Why? Where is he?
Off somewhere hiding.
I mean, sulking.
Uh, in that case, he’s in the forest,
he always goes there when he feels like moping.
Huh?
So? Back to your usual cool self yet?
Not 100%
Well this might help you to quit sulking.
We’ve got some incredible news.
I don’t believe it, I’m actually writing the final entry in the Lyoko Travel Logbook.
Can you imagine?
Aelita?
Aelita, are you ok?
I--I--
Do you think it’s the anti-virus?
No, it’s just an energy slump.
I’ll go and lie down in my room for a minute or two.
(PANICKED GASPING)
Oh Aelita, I didn’t even see you standing there.
But that’s hardly surprising, you’re such a wallflower.
How can you expect a guy to notice you someday?
I’m not talking about Jeremie, of course,
he’s already married to a computer chip.
I’m mean a real guy, you know?
Look at me, for instance, I’m really pretty, and attractive.
But that’s not all, I’m also funny, and intelligent,
sweet and very attentive to others.
Huh? Just what I was saying She’s so unremarkable,
you don’t even realize that she’s gone.
Oh no!
Jeremie, this is awful.
It sure is, Xana is attacking!
Aelita?
I’m here.
You are?
Where?
Right in front of you.
But I’m… I’m invisible.
You’re what?
Hey!
Oh, sorry.
Could this be Xana’s attack?
Quick, to the factory!
Uh oh, what’s that?
A nice little doggy, I hope.
(GROWLS)
No, a big bad wolf, Odd.
Uh, when you’re faced with a pack of wolves,
what do you do?
You run!
Konnichiwa, you’ve Yumi’s mobile,
leave me a message.
Yumi, meet us at the factory,
there’s a bug.
Oh no.
Let’s go, come on.
Ulrich, hurry up!
(GROWLING)
Ulrich!
(WHIMPERING)
Don’t look down!
Concentrate on your hand grips,
and don’t think about anything else!
Yeah, that’s it, keep climbing!
Just a little further!
I gotcha!
I’m here, Jeremie.
It isn’t Xana,
it’s a bug in the anti-virus.
I have to deactivate it,
but it’s gonna take a little while.
What about the activated tower?
What’s the attack?
I have no idea.
Yumi!
We’ve got a big problem, Jeremie,
We’re in the forest with a pack of wolves possessed by Xana.
Oh no, Aelita can’t go and deactivate the tower by herself.
We’ll do our best,
I’ll keep you posted.
Jeremie, virtualize me on Lyoko so I can deactivate the tower.
No way, we have to wait.
Wait for what? For them to be devoured?
We have no choice.
Your foot ok?
Good thing you weren’t wearing sandals.
(GROWLING)
Oh great.
A flying wolf.
Jeremie, I’m here.
It’s good to be visible again.
I’ve programmed the overwing for you.
And the activated tower shouldn’t be far.
(GROWLING)
This is when the kind hunters usually come to the rescue, right?
(SCREAMING)
Ulrich!
But.
Huh?
It’s a decoy!
They-- They’re just images!
That Xana’s even sly-er than I thought.
No Scyphozoa in sight, Jeremie.
Anyways, be careful.
(GROWLING)
Uh oh, this one’s real.
So are these two.
(PHONE RINGS)
Jeremie!
How’s it going?
It sure is no picnic over here.
Hang on, Aelita is almost at the activated tower.
What’s going on?
Jeremie, we’ve got a problem.
Yumi?
Yeah?
The anti-virus I injected into Aelita has modified her virtual signature.
The tower doesn’t recognize her any longer!
You mean she can’t deactivate them anymore?
Exactly. That is,
until I manage to extract that dumb bugged virus.
But she’s all alone on Lyoko,
and I can’t devirtualize her.
Ok, we’ll be right there.
Aelita needs our help.
Glad to hear it,
but how do you plan on getting out of this jam?
We split up,
I’ll take care of them.
Are you crazy?
Go on, I said. Ok?
I may have vertigo,
but I can handle a few flea-bitten mongrels.
On three, get going.
You mean one two and go?
Or do you mean one two three and go?
Go!
Calvary is on the way, Aelita.
Careful, behind you!
No!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
You can start the process, Jeremie.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Yumi.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
You know what you have to do,
your vehicles are on the way.
Follow the trail!
The activated tower is inside the cavern.
How’s Ulrich?
No news.
(BARKING)
Yumi, Odd, move it!
Huh?
Jeremie.
Well done, Odd.
Odd, you’re the only one who can do anything, now.
Jeremie, how’s it going?
A complete mess, and you?
Ditto.
(SCREAMING)
Ulrich!
Oh no, the’ve got guard dogs.
(SHIVERING)
Laser Arrows!
You ok?
Jeremie, how’s it going with the anti-virus?
I’m working on it.
What about Ulrich?
Ulrich!
I’ve gotta help him!
Wait, the anti-virus is deactivated.
Aelita you can get into the tower now.
Hope this works.
It’s ok, Jeremie.
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Tower deactivated.
(WHIMPERING)
Launch a return to the past!
Hurry up!
Return to the past now.
First one to the top.
Well?
No thanks.
You chicken?
You got vertigo, or what?
Yeah, what about it?
No worse than being afraid of spiders.
Hey, how did you know that?
I have my spies.
(CHUCKLING)
Anyway, see ya around, Spiderman.
So, Aelita,
what’s it like being invisible?
I always wanted to be like, you know,
Sue in the Fantastic Four.
(LAUGHING)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS